# Ahosan Kabir

Dhaka, Bangladesh



kaziahosan1998@gmail.com



01747024208



linkedin.com/in/ahosan-kabir-48a893213

#### Summary

I am Ahosan Kabir. A MERN stack developer. I have also experience in the teaching profession. almost 3 years I include myself in the teaching profession besides I learn new skills so that I can go with this updated world. my experience is always learning the things you want to go forward for yourself and help others.

Things I kept in my mind -

Goals should cover every aspect of life, whether physical, mental, career, or fun.

Goals should be measurable and perfectly challenging

Should not be a dream goal instead make it actionable.

#### **Experience**

#### Graduate Student

Web Development Jan 2021 - Present (2 years 2 months)

#### Assistant teacher ( Science )

Kawsar Ahmmed School and College, Gajipur Jan 2022 - Sep 2022 (9 months)

#### **Education**



### National University | Bangladesh

Bachelor of Science - BS, Chemistry 2017 - 2022

### Govt. Shaheed Bulbul College, Pabna

HSC, Science 2014 - 2016

### Radhanagar Majumdar Academy

SSC, Science

#### **Licenses & Certifications**



## Responsive Web Design - freeCodeCamp

#### **Skills**

Teamwork • Self Learning • Node.js • React.js • English • Communication • Front-end Development • Leadership • Teaching